Guide to the New York University Archives Collection on 2020 Virtual Commencement Celebrations Webpages MC.354
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Collection on Virtual Commencement Celebrations Webpages
May-December 2020
New York University Archives
New York University
New York University. Gallatin Division
New York University. College of Arts and Science
New York University. School of Law
New York University. Tandon School of Engineering
Leonard N. Stern School of Business
New York University. Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service.
New York University. College of Global Public Health
Steinhardt School of Education
New York University. College of Nursing
New York University in Abu Dhabi
New York University. College of Dentistry
MC.354
70 websites in 70 archived websites.
New York University Archives Collection on Virtual Commencement Celebrations Webpages documents the virtual commencement proceedings for New York University and its school ceremonies in response to the COVID-19 pandemic. The collection contains video streams of the ceremonies, awards, student profiles, messages from deans, names of graduates, and commencement programs.
Conditions Governing Access
Material pertaining to individual student records may be restricted in accordance with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA). Please contact the Archives with specific questions regarding access to such records.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Websites were selected by Janet Bunde and Nicole Greenhouse and captured through the use of Archive-It in May and June 2020. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. The accession numbers associated with these websites are 2020.039, 2020.042, 2021.004, 2021.005, and 2021.007.
Take Down Policy
Archived websites are made accessible for purposes of education and research. NYU Libraries have given attribution to rights holders when possible; however, due to the nature of archival collections, we are not always able to identify this information.
If you hold the rights to materials in our archived websites that are unattributed, please let us know so that we may maintain accurate information about these materials.
If you are a rights holder and are concerned that you have found material on this website for which you have not granted permission (or is not covered by a copyright exception under US copyright laws), you may request the removal of the material from our site by submitting a notice, with the elements described below, to the special.collections@nyu.edu.
Please include the following in your notice: Identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; your contact information, such as an address, telephone number, and email address; a statement that you are the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed and that you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and made under penalty of perjury; and your physical or electronic signature. Upon receiving a notice that includes the details listed above, we will remove the allegedly infringing material from public view while we assess the issues identified in your notice.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by date then by record group.
Historical Note
In March 2020, New York University shifted to remote activities due to the COVID-19 pandemic. This led to the postponement of in-person commencement events and a pivot to virtual events in May 2020.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
Scope and Contents
New York University Archives Collection on Virtual Commencement Celebrations Webpages documents the virtual commencement proceedings for New York University and its school ceremonies from 2020 and 2021. The collection contains video streams of the ceremonies, awards, student profiles, messages from deans, names of graduates, and commencement programs. The collection also includes all university commencement proceedings.
Commencement ceremonies; Video recordings.
- Series I: Commencement 2020
  - Office of External Affairs, Commencement and Special Events (RG 7.4)
    - Commencement, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      Scope and Contents
      This webpage provides information about and a link to the virtual celebration of all 2020 graduates of New York University.
    - Grad Alley, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      Webpage containing information on the virtual reality grad alley experience and information about Empire State Building glowing violet for the graduating class on May 19, 2020.
    - School Ceremonies, May-June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage collocates information on the University's various school-based virtual celebrations of graduates in 2020.
  - College of Arts and Science (RG 19)
    - College of Arts and Science Baccalaureate Livestream, May-June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      Webpage for the livestream tribute to the NYU College of Arts and Science Class of 2020 on May 19, 2020.
    - College of Arts and Science Dean's Letter, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides information about and a link to the virtual celebration of graduates of the College of Arts and Science.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences (RG 20)
    - GSAS Convocation, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides information about and a link to the virtual celebration for graduates of the Graduate School of Arts and Science.
  - Liberal Studies Program (RG 21.47)
    - Global Liberal Studies Graduation Celebration for the Class of 2020, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - Liberal Studies Marching Order, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - Liberal Studies Marching Order, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - Liberal Studies Service and Leadership Celebration, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
  - School of Law (RG 22)
    - Honoring the Graduating Class of 2020, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage includes a virtual celebration of the graduating class of 2020 from the NYU School of Law as well as names of all graduates.
    - NYU Law Graduation 2020, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides information about the virtual celebrations for the graduates of the School of Law.
    - NYU Law: A Virtual Celebration for the Graduating Class of 2020, January 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
  - College of Dentistry (RG 25)
    - NYU Dentistry Class of 2020 Virtual Celebration, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
  - Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development (RG 26)
    - Celebrate the Steinhardt Class of 2020, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides information about and a link to the virtual celebration for graduates of the Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development.
    - Celebrating NYU Steinhardt's Class of 2020, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
  - Stern School of Business (Undergraduate) (RG 27)
    - Class of 2020, December 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - Executive Programs 2020 Virtual Celebration, December 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - FAQs for Stern's 2020 Virtual Celebrations, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides information about the virtual celebration for graduates of the Stern School of Business.
    - NYU Stern Class of 2020 Undergraduate Virtual Celebration, January 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    - NYU Stern Undergraduate Class of 2020 Celebration, May-June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      Webpage celebration the Stern Undergraduate Class of 2020. Contains a message from Dean Sundaram and Vice Dean Whitelaw and listing of graduates with audio files pronouncing their names.
    - NYU Stern Undergraduate College Class of 2020 Graduates, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - Stern Virtual Celebrations, May-June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides information about the virtual celebrations for graduates of the Stern School of Business.
    - Undergraduate Class of 2020 Celebration, December 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
  - Stern School of Business (Graduate) (RG 28)
    - Graduate Class of 2020 Celebration, December 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - NYU Stern Graduate Class of 2020 Celebration, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - NYU Stern Graduate Class of 2020 Celebration Program, May-June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - Stern Graduate Marching Order Commencement Website, May-December 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
  - School of Professional Studies (RG 32)
    - NYU SPS 2020 Graduate Virtual Celebration, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      Webpage for the virtual celebration livestream for SPS graduates on May 18, 2020.
    - NYU SPS 2020 Undergraduate Virtual Celebration, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      Webpage for the virtual celebration livestream for SPS undergraduates on May 21, 2020.
    - NYU SPS Graduates Graduation Ceremonies, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides information about and a link to the virtual celebration for graduates of the School for Professional Studies.
  - Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service (RG 33)
    - NYU Wagner Virtual Grad Celebration 2020, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      Youtube video of the Wagner virtual commencement on May 21, 2020.
    - NYU Wagner Virtual Grad Celebration 2020, May-June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides information about the virtual celebrations for the graduates of NYU Wagner.
  - Silver School of Social Work (RG 34)
    - Congratulations to the Class of 2020, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (RG 35)
    - Salute 2020, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage includes a message to graduates of the Tisch School of the Arts from faculty and staff of the School.
    - Tisch Graduation, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
  - Gallatin School of Individualized Study (RG 36)
    - Gallatin Graduation Ceremonies, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides information about the postponement of commencement ceremonies for the Gallatin School of Individualized Study.
    - Gallatin Homepage, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      The Gallatin homepage captured on May 2020 contains a carousel with the names of Gallatin graduates. It also contains links to Gallatin program with awardees and honors and a tribute to the class of 2020.
  - Tandon School of Engineering (RG 48)
    - Class of 2020 Virtual Celebration, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      Redirect to the Tandon Class of 2020 virtual celebration.
    - NYU Tandon Class of 2020 Virtual Celebration, January 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    - Tandon 2020 Commencement Awards, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      Tandon awardees in Academic and Student Affairs, Applied Physics, Chemical and Biomolecular Engineering, Civil and Urban Engineering, Computer science and Engineering, Electrical and Coputer Engineering, Finance and Risk Engineering, Mathematics, Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering, Technology, Culture, and Society, and Technology Management and Innovation.
    - Tandon Class of 2020: Your Vision. Your Future, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      Graduating student profiles on their ideas for the future.
    - Tandon School of Engineering Class of 2020 Virtual Celebration, May-December 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      Landing page containing a video for the virtual commencement, class of 2020 featured student profiles, and commencement awards.
    - Tandon School of Engineering Commencement 2020, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides information about and a link to the virtual celebration of all 2020 graduates of the Tandon School of Engineering.
    - Tandon School of Engineering Virtual Celebration, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      Webpage with information on the Tandom School of Engineering virtual celebration, calendar of events, eligibility for graduation, and rules for submission to the "What's Your Vision" video.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi (RG 49)
    - Class of 2020: NYUAD's 10th Anniversary, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - Congratulations #NYUAD2020: Commencement Pre-Show, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - Congratulations #NYUAD2020: Part 1, January 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    - Congratulations #NYUAD2020: Part 2, January 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    - New York University Abu Dhabi 2020 Commencement - Live Version, January 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    - New York University Abu Dhabi Seventh Commencement Exercises Program, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - NYU Abu Dhabi Class of 2020: A Tribute, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - NYU Abu Dhabi Commencement 2020, May-June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides information about the virtual celebrations for graduates of NYU Abu Dhabi.
    - NYU Abu Dhabi Commencement 2020 Magazine, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - NYUAD Class of 2020: Global Tribute, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - NYUAD Class of 2020: Travel Memories, January 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    - Vice Chancellor Mariët Westermann Congratulates #NYUAD2020, January 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    - We Are Not Strangers (NYU Abu Dhabi), January 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
  - NYU Shanghai (RG 50)
    - NYU Shanghai Commencement 2020, May-December 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides information about the NYU Shanghai virtual commencement celebrations. It includes news release on Jack Ma's commencement address, commencement program, senior profiles, student honors and rewards, a photo gallery, and an alumni video.
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing (RG 52)
    - NYU Meyers Class of 2020 Virtual Celebration, January 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    - NYU Meyers Program for 2020 Virtual Celebration for Graduating Students, June-December 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - Virtual Celebration for the NYU Rory Meyers College of Nursing Class of 2020, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides information about and a link to the virtual celebration for graduates of the Rory Meyers College of Nursing.
  - School of Global Public Health (RG 53)
    - NYU School of Global Public Health Graduation Celebration 2020, June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    - NYU School of Global Public Health Graduation Celebration 2020, January 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    - School of Global Public Health Graduation Celebration 2020, May 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
      This webpage provides inforrmation about and a link to the virtual celebration for graduates of the School of Global Public Health.